MEGAN HUTCHISON

COMPOSITOR

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Wellington New Zealand

PHONE

+64 27 478-0293

EMAIL

meganhvfx@gmail.com

LINKS

IMDB

Linkedin

Showreel

SKILLS

Nuke

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

ShotGrid

• • • • 0

OS: Mac/PC/Linux

.

Silhouette

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Photoshop

• • • o o

Mocha

• • 0 0 0

RECENT PROJECTS

Peacemaker: Season 2 - Dir. James Gunn

Fountain of Youth - Dir. Guy Richie

Furiosa: A Mad Max Saga -Dir. George Miller

Nyad - Dir. Jimmy Chin & Elizabeth Chai Vasarhelyi

Bullet Train - Dir. David Leitch

PROFILE

Passionate and dedicated Compositor, with over a decade of experience in VFX. Self-motivated and a fast learner, with a keen eye for detail. Able to thrive in any team environment, with a commitment to continuous learning, while quickly adapting to new technologies and workflows. Dual New Zealand/Canadian citizen.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Compositor, Wētā FX

Wellington

Sep 2024 — Present

- Key abilities include; keying, edge work, creature integration, script optimizing while also being able to merging creativity with technical precision.
- Worked as a part of both large and small show teams, and can effectively communicate with peers, prod and leads/supes.
- · Upskilled by working within the deep pipeline, and on full CG creature shots.

Compositor, DNEG

Vancouver

May 2021 — Jun 2024

- Key abilities included; keying (bluescreens and sandscreens), projections, tech checks, and integrating env elements and edge work.
- · Worked within tight deadlines and with teams throughout the world.
- · Organized and self motivated, learning on-the-job while balancing deadlines.

Roto/Prep Supervisor, DNEG

Vancouver

May 2015 — May 2021

- Briefed shots from off-site vendors, then QC roto/prep renders, attended turnover, target and bidding meetings
- · Includes nine months in 2018/2019 in Montreal to set up department

Roto/Prep Artist, ILM

Vancouver

Mar 2014 — Mar 2015

- Worked across many shows with complex cleanups and CG fixes in Commodore, the proprietary software at ILM.
- · Had offsite supervisors, requiring open and effective communication.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts & Commerce, Victoria University

Wellington

Feb 2006 — Nov 2009

BA Majoring in Media Studies & Film, BCom Majoring in Marketing

REFERENCES

References available upon request